<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.discoveryplus" version="1.6.7" name="discovery+" provider-name="Dis90">
<requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
  <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
  <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.2.4"/>
  <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" version="2.4.6"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
  <provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.service" library="services.py"/>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <summary lang="en">discovery+</summary>
  <description lang="en"></description>
  <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
  <assets>
    <icon>resources/icon.png</icon> 
    <fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>
  </assets>
  <news>
    v1.6.7 (19.12.2021)
    - Playback progress updating is now blocked only for Live TV
    - Fix realmservice on Kodi 18
    v1.6.6 (19.12.2021)
    - Fixes to realmservice in case folder or file is missing
    v1.6.5 (18.12.2021)
    - Fix channel pages with only livestream
    - Country specific content rating system (mpaa)
    - Rename favorites to My List (context menu add/remove from My List)
    - Get country specific configs from discovery+ realm service. No more hard coded values (except d+ India)
    - Fix for listing shows without seasons when seasonsonly setting is set to true
    - Home -> For You -> Networks or Network Rail is now translated to Channels
    v1.6.4 (15.12.2021)
    - More fixes and improvements to EPG data (European countries)
    - Option to set cookie in add-on settings
    v1.6.3 (14.12.2021)
    - Fix listing Shows page (UK)
    v1.6.2 (14.12.2021)
    - Support for switching profile (US and EU)
    - Fix EPG for sport events (European countries)
    v1.6.1 (14.12.2021)
    - Fix IPTV Manager EPG (European countries)
    v1.6.0 (13.12.2021)
    - Support for new API in European countries. You need to get new cookies from browser.
    - Updated player properties to same in all countries.
    v1.5.24 (14.9.2021)
    - Fixed season list when data contains empty collection
    v1.5.23 (19.8.2021)
    - New setting for only listing seasons in season listing (EU countries)
    - If setting for hiding non season categories from seasons page is enabled, you can enable setting for flatten TV show seasons if only one season (EU countries)
    v1.5.22 (14.8.2021)
    - Promoted items are now displayed (rows with large banner but no title) - European countries
    v1.5.21 (26.7.2021)
    - Fixed season list displaying wrong metadata in some European countries 
  </news>
</extension>
</addon>
